{
    "subject": "resource/Best_Buddies_International",
    "predicate": "property/foundedDate",
    "object": "1989",
    "human_readable": "Best Buddies International was founded in 1989.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9158995747566223,
            "question": "When was Best Buddies International founded?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5842301845550537,
            "question": "Are there any notable achievements or milestones for Best Buddies International?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5254599452018738,
            "question": "What is the purpose of Best Buddies International?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5046103000640869,
            "question": "What are some ways individuals can get involved with Best Buddies International?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.40512198209762573,
            "question": "How has Best Buddies International contributed to fostering inclusion?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3933274447917938,
            "question": "Does Best Buddies International operate globally?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.35720106959342957,
            "question": "What impact has Best Buddies International had on its beneficiaries?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3478493392467499,
            "question": "Who are the beneficiaries of Best Buddies International's programs?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.30763867497444153,
            "question": "What types of programs does Best Buddies International offer?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.27472370862960815,
            "question": "What challenges does Best Buddies International face in its mission?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Best Buddies International was founded in 1989.",
            "html": "dbpedia_3410_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What types of programs does Best Buddies International offer?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3410_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Who are the beneficiaries of Best Buddies International's programs?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3410_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What impact has Best Buddies International had on its beneficiaries?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3410_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3410_107.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3410_22.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3410_3.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3410_44.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3410_47.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3410_52.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3410_58.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3410_71.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3410_75.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3410_94.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe documents provided state that \"Best Buddies International is a nonprofit 501(c)(3) organization dedicated to establishing a global volunteer movement that creates opportunities for one-to-one friendships, integrated employment, leadership development, and inclusive living for individuals with intellectual and developmental disabilities (IDD).\" They also mention that it was founded in 1989 by Anthony K. Shriver, which supports the statement \"Best Buddies International was founded in 1989.\""
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Less Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}